[Music]
hello and thank you for tuning in for
another product review from Sharp's
Shooting Supply my name is Tyler sharp
and let's dive on in So today we're
going to be covering the sour P320
M18 this firearm is chambered in 9mm and
features a 17 +1 capacity
magazine with a 3.9 in
Barrel this model became the new US
military firearm here not too long ago
and uh it's pretty easy to see why it's
a nice nice feeling firearm that's
something a little bit different than
what they've gone with in the past this
model does feature the coyote PVD finish
that really helps fight corrosion and
keeps the the rust resistance
High there is an ambidextrious safety
and an ambidextrious slide
release and an ambidextrious mag release
so this firearm is truly an
ambidextrious fire uh firearm it does
feature a three dot night sight picture
and it has an Optics cut
rail there is a m1913 accessory
accessory rail on the bottom to handle
all your Light and Laser needs and this
firearm does come in at 20 8.1 oz so
it's a little bit on the heavy side for
a concealed carry firearm but not too
bad initially it does feel a little
topheavy but once you get that 17 plus1
magazine fully loaded it's really going
to balance the firearm out
nice it is Striker Fired and it is
compatible with the Sig Romeo and lull
uh red
dots we talked about this manual safety
right here so that's a that's a nice
feature to have on guns I kind of prefer
my concealed carrier Firearms to have a
safety but it uh definitely isn't a deal
breaker um this firearm does feature a
serialized uh fire control unit so you
can swap out the trigger and the fire
control unit between different frame
sizes I believe you can go uh bigger and
there might even be a smaller version I
can't remember off the top of my head
but that was one of the military
requirements was to have a different
grip and frame size options from the
factory it does feature a 4.5 lb trigger
so a nice nice crisp trigger that's kind
of middle of the road on the
weight and there were some drop safety
concerns in the past we can't get
through a P320 review without mentioning
the uh drop safety concerns uh by the
time the M18 version hit the civilian
Market the problem had been resolved by
6 hour so
they're still recommending that you
double check the serial number to make
sure that that firearm did have the uh
upgraded safety components
installed but uh this particular one
that I'm holding has been uh has been
corrected and it it sure does feel nice
another neat feature you can tell the
civilian model of the M18 by the serial
number and all civilian models begin
with an M so just a kind of a neat
little concept there right off the bat
um 6 hour made in America so you have a
great americanmade
firearm that will definitely hold up for
you so let's check out what's in the
box you got two not just one but two 21
+ one capacity magazines so you've got
the extended magazines in the Box the
youth handgun safety notice they did
include an M18 patch for all those patch
collectors out there of course the Sig
hour warranty or the user manual
warranty information and a
sticker and Sig sour really pushes their
line of
ammunition so not a whole lot of extra
accessories in the Box other than the
two mags and that is enough to make make
me
happy so that is the Sig sour P320 M18
in a nutshell great firearm would make
an excellent conceal carry piece or even
just an everyday carry or a great um
target shooting pistol it is a pleasure
to shoot I have it a P320 myself not
this exact model but I sure do enjoy
carrying my 3 P320 great firearm it's
never let me down and with that sigire
reputation I don't expect it to so swing
by the shop check it out we appreciate
you tuning in for this product review
and we will catch you on the next one